thebiglot.com 2005-04-02

# Privacy Policy

---  

|   
  
---  
  
**Privacy Policy**  
  
TheBigLot.com is a classified service provided by Adventis, Inc.  Adventis, Inc. established TheBiglot.com as a means for customers to achieve unprecedented online exposure for their vehicle, while at the same time having access to unparalleled customer service. TheBigLot.com recognizes and understands your concerns about privacy and the use of your personal information.  This Privacy Policy is intended to summarize the privacy practices of the [www.thebiglot.com](http://www.thebiglot.com/). 

**Personal Information from Visitors**

In order to facilitate the sale of vehicles and related services online, it is imperative that personal information is collected. Personal information on TheBiglot.com falls into two distinct categories: 1) personal information that visitors volunteer and 2) tracking information that does not identify you as an individual but that assists us in tracking affiliate referrals.

When filling out an ad or form on TheBigLot.com, visitors must volunteer personal information. "Personal information" may include name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and specific vehicle information. Personal information is used for three main purposes: 1) as contact information for anyone interested in purchasing a vehicle; 2) to help us provide fulfillment services in connection with goods and services ordered by you; and 3) to offer more information about our service. Thus, as a customer of TheBigLot.com, you will be contacted by potential buyers. We may contact you about your account or send you information directly related to the purpose for which you have registered. As a visitor to TheBigLot.com, the contact information you volunteer may be used by TheBigLot.com or its affiliates to offer you more information about our services. In particular, please understand that when seeking a quote on a new vehicle your contact information will be forwarded to both an affiliate and dealerships to fulfill your request for information. 

As a customer, you must understand your information is available to everyone when posting an ad on the Internet. We cannot control how potential buyers or businesses use your contact information. If a business calls you about your vehicle and you're not interested in their service, tell them: "Put me on your Do Not Call list" and hang up. If a business e-mails you and you're not interested, DO NOT RESPOND to the e-mail. Do not even respond to request the removal of your name from their mailing list. Many companies send out e-mails just to verify that you have a legitimate e-mail address. You also need to remember that your personal information will continue to be available on the Internet until you notify us to cancel your ad. You may discontinue your ad by calling us at 1 (800) 430-1965 ( _Please note that refund requests must be submitted in writing_ ) or writing to: 

Adventis Inc.  
Attn: Customer Care  
P.O. Box 1671  
Roanoke, VA  
24008  

If you wish to obtain a hard copy of the personal information contained in your ad, contact our Customer Care department at 1 (800) 430-1965, ext. 2 and request that we fax you a copy of the information. 

**Amending Personal Information**

As a customer, you may also make corrections or updates to the personal information that you provide us.  With respect to your personal contact information, (i.e., your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address) you must contact our Customer Care department at 1 (800) 430-1965, ext. 2.  With respect to specific vehicle information, you may either contact Customer Care or make changes online.  When making changes online, simply click "Find Your Ad" on the TheBigLot.com home page, enter your Customer ID number, click "GO", and then enter the Pin Number given to you when you purchased the ad.  Please be aware that this information is located on a non-secure site.    

**Use of Cookies**

In order for TheBigLot.com to better track affiliate referrals, and thus better target our services to you, we place a small text file on your hard drive, called a "cookie".  Cookies do not contain any personal data, they do not damage your files, and they do not allow us or anyone else to access your personally identifiable information - they simply tell us what site referred you to us.  Cookies may contain such information as an IP address, DNS host name, and/or browser type.  We may aggregate this information in order to analyze website traffic figures and technical issues.  We may also share aggregate (not individual) site referral statistics with advertisers and other third parties, but again, this information will not include any personally identifiable information.  If you do not wish to receive cookies on your hard drive, most web browsers have a help option that will explain how to reject certain cookies or to disable them entirely.

**Policy on Children's Personal Information**

We do not knowingly collect personal data from children.  To ensure that children's privacy is respected on our Web site, we will not knowingly allow anyone under the age of 13 to provide any personally identifying information. In the event that someone under the age of 13 indicates that they have provided personally identifiable information to us, we will immediately remove that information from the website.  Such information will not be sold to any third party for any purpose whatsoever.

**Contact Information for Affiliates**

TheBigLot.com also runs an affiliate referral program.  Technical contact information is required for such partnerships.  "Technical contact information" includes name, name of employer, business address, and e-mail address.  Technical contact information is only used to carry out the purpose of each partnership.  This information is not sold to third parties.  The technical contact information is collected on a non-secure registration page.   

**Links on TheBigLot.com**

In order to better serve you, and make your visit to our site more worthwhile, TheBigLot.com has links on the homepage to other third party Web service providers.  Those third party Web service providers specialize in pricing new and used cars and obtaining vehicle history reports and insurance quotes.  When you choose to visit those sites, we are not responsible for their privacy policies or how they treat user information.  You should review the privacy policies of these third parties when supplying personally identifiable information, as they will likely differ from this one.

TheBigLot.com strives to protect your information off-line as well.  We restrict access to personal financial information to those employees who need to process your account and/or refunds, such as a customer service representative or the Chief Financial Officer.

Finally, under certain circumstances, TheBigLot.com may disclose personal information when required by law. 

**Where is Personal Information stored?**

The security of the information you provide to TheBigLot.com is important to us.  Information that is collected by TheBigLot.com and TheBigLot.com website is stored on in-house controlled databases and servers.  This includes any information provided by visitors, even those who do not order our service.  We have implemented security policies, rules, and technical measures to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of sensitive information under our control.   In particular, all credit card transactions are protected by the latest Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology.  SSL is the Internet standard for secured transactions.  If you have any questions about the use of your credit card information, please contact our Customer Care department at 1-800- 430-1965, ext. 2, or via e-mail at web@thebiglot.com. 

**Possible Future Uses of Information**

In the unlikely event that the assets of Adventis, Inc. and TheBigLot.com are acquired by another company, information on our customers/visitors would be among the transferred assets. 

TheBigLot.com reserves the right to change our Privacy Policy as business needs require.  Any changes will be posted to our website in a timely manner, and will become effective upon posting.  This statement and the policies outlined here are not intended to and do not give you any contractual or other legal rights.  To the extent not contradicted by this Privacy Policy, this Privacy Policy also incorporates the provisions of our User Agreement.

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions, concerns, or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact our Operations Manager directly at 1-800-430-1965, ext. 139, or e-mail at info@thebiglot.com. 

For any other questions, please contact our Customer Care department at 1-800-430-1965, ext. 2, or e-mail at info@thebiglot.com.  Our Customer Care hours of operation are Monday through Thursday 9:00 a.m. to 9:00 p.m., Friday 9:00 a.m. to 6:00 p.m., and Saturday 1:00 p.m. to  5:00 p.m., Eastern Time.  Our mailing address is: Adventis, Inc., P.O. Box 1671, Roanoke, Virginia 24008.
